<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bolivia on SATO South America</title>
    <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/tags/bolivia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bolivia on SATO South America</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://satosouthamerica.com/tags/bolivia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Day Bolivia Experience</title>
      <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/10-day-bolivia-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/10-day-bolivia-experience/</guid>
      <description>This week and half will allow you to explore one of South America&amp;rsquo;s best kept secrets; Bolivia. The 10 day Bolivia vacation package starts in breathtaking La Paz will be the starting point of this adventure, exploring the blue waters of lake Titicaca, the beautiful city of Sucre and the unique Uyuni Salt Flats and Siloli Desert.
Highlights  Have your breath taken away by the views of La Paz from a cable car Sail the azure deep blue waters of Lake Titicaca to the Isla del Sol (Sun Island) Walk through the colonial center of Sucre, Bolivia’s second capital Be breath taken by the altitude and the history of Potosi and its (in)famous silver mine Stargaze at the stars reflecting on the shallow waters of the Uyuni Salt Flat at night</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>14 Day Peru &amp; Bolivia Andean Experience</title>
      <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/14-day-peru-bolivia-andean-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/14-day-peru-bolivia-andean-experience/</guid>
      <description>These 14 days will allow you to get to experience the best of the Andes region that connects these two countries. Machu Picchu and the Inca history on one side and the unique beauty of the Uyuni Salt Flats and Siloli Desert on the other end, with in the middle the breathtaking Lake Titicaca as well as the Quechua and Aymara Cultures that unite these two countries.
Highlights  Visit the ancient city of Cusco with its eclectic beauty from Inca and Colonial times Discover the most impressive archeological site on the continent; Machu Picchu Explore the mysterious deep blue waters of Lake Titicaca Travel through the Uyuni Salt Flats and awe at the star filled skies hosted at night Drive through the moonlike Siloli Desert with its strangely colored lagoons  Day by Day Day 1; Welcome to Lima, the City of King welcomes you with open arms and amazing food</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>