<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chile on SATO South America</title>
    <link>https://sato-southamerica.netlify.com/tags/chile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chile on SATO South America</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sato-southamerica.netlify.com/tags/chile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Day Argentina Experience</title>
      <link>https://sato-southamerica.netlify.com/post/10-day-argentina-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sato-southamerica.netlify.com/post/10-day-argentina-experience/</guid>
      <description>This trip will allow you to grasp the soul of the massive country and its proud culture. We will start our 10 day Argentina vacation package in the city of Buenos Aires with the Iguazu Falls as your next stop before heading to the far south to explore the beauty of Patagonia, its lakes and glaciers in El Calafate and Ushuaia.
Highlights  Stroll through Recoleta and enjoy Buenos Aires Porteño style; Tango, wine and beef.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Day Chile Experience</title>
      <link>https://sato-southamerica.netlify.com/post/10-day-chile-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sato-southamerica.netlify.com/post/10-day-chile-experience/</guid>
      <description>During this 10 day Chile vacation package you will have the chance to get to know some of Chile’s most enigmatic destinations and attractions. From the metropolitan capital Santiago we will head north to the Atacama Desert for amazing days and spectacular nights. From here we will head to the far south to explore the granite mountain peaks of the famous Torres del Paine Park in Patagonia
Highlights  Enjoy cultural Santiago perched between the Pacific and the Andes Taste some of Chile’s finest reds and whites at one of the famous Wine Valleys</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>