<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Peru on SATO South America</title>
    <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/tags/peru/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Peru on SATO South America</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://satosouthamerica.com/tags/peru/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Day Peru Experience</title>
      <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/10-day-peru-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/10-day-peru-experience/</guid>
      <description>These 10 days will allow you to discover the essence of Peru, its archeology and landscapes. Taste the culinary delights of Lima, wander through the cobblestoned streets of Cusco, awe at the beauty of Machu Picchu and spot wildlife in the depths of the Amazon Rainforest.
Highlights  Explore Cosmopolitan Lima Visit colonial Cusco Shop for local textiles on the Pisac market Hike Huayna Picchu for the best views of Machu Picchu below Enjoy the sound, color and smell of the Amazon Rainforest  Day by Day Day 1; On arrival to Lima we will welcome you and take you to your hotel to unwind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Day Machu Picchu &amp; Galapagos Islands Experience</title>
      <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/12-day-machu-picchu-galapagos-islands-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/12-day-machu-picchu-galapagos-islands-experience/</guid>
      <description>This 12 day Peru &amp;amp; Ecuador vacation package will allow you to get to enjoy two of the most spectacular highlights in South America; majestic Machu Picchu in the Andes and the curious Galapagos Islands remotely located in the Pacific Ocean. Culture and Wildlife meanwhile traveling through vibrant cities and some of the continents most spectacular sceneries.
Highlights  Visit the old Inca Capitals of Cusco and Quito, nowadays turned vibrant cities Explore the Sacred Valley leading to the lost city of the Incas Discover the most impressive archeological site on the continent; Machu Picchu Enjoy an island hopping program on some of the world’s most remote islands Get up-and-close with unique fauna and flora of the Galapagos  Day by Day Day 1; Arrive to the City of Kings; Lima where you will spend the night</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>14 Day Peru &amp; Bolivia Andean Experience</title>
      <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/14-day-peru-bolivia-andean-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/14-day-peru-bolivia-andean-experience/</guid>
      <description>These 14 days will allow you to get to experience the best of the Andes region that connects these two countries. Machu Picchu and the Inca history on one side and the unique beauty of the Uyuni Salt Flats and Siloli Desert on the other end, with in the middle the breathtaking Lake Titicaca as well as the Quechua and Aymara Cultures that unite these two countries.
Highlights  Visit the ancient city of Cusco with its eclectic beauty from Inca and Colonial times Discover the most impressive archeological site on the continent; Machu Picchu Explore the mysterious deep blue waters of Lake Titicaca Travel through the Uyuni Salt Flats and awe at the star filled skies hosted at night Drive through the moonlike Siloli Desert with its strangely colored lagoons  Day by Day Day 1; Welcome to Lima, the City of King welcomes you with open arms and amazing food</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>