<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SATO South America</title>
    <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SATO South America</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 21:49:20 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://satosouthamerica.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>South America - Wines &amp; Spirits; a small introduction</title>
      <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/blog/south-america-wines-spirits-a-small-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://satosouthamerica.com/blog/south-america-wines-spirits-a-small-introduction/</guid>
      <description>For those a little familiar with the world of wines Chile and Argentina have been long time players on the international wine market. In many European supermarkets you can find Chilean wines at better prices than their European competitors and the international wine market only keeps growing. In size the Argentinean producers are close to their Chilean counterparts and these wines can also easily be found in most supermarkets or liquor stores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where in South America Should I Go</title>
      <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/blog/where-in-south-america-should-i-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://satosouthamerica.com/blog/where-in-south-america-should-i-go/</guid>
      <description>Peru Top destinations;  Machu Picchu Cusco Sacred Valley Lima Amazon Rainforest Lake Titicaca Colca Canyon  Weather; Large variety of climates and microclimates (Arid, Temperate &amp;amp; Tropical)
Interests; Archeology, Food &amp;amp; Wildlife
A quick look; South America doesn’t get much more evocative of generations gone by than Peru. Its mix of ancient civilizations and unparalleled archaeology, set among some of the most extraordinary views on the planet, means few destinations have as much to offer visitors as Peru.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 15:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://satosouthamerica.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to SATO South America. We are the South America travel specialist providing tailor-made vacation packages to all major South American destinations. Traveling with SATO South America allows you to;
 Fully customize your itinerary Deal with South America based travel consultants Rely on experts to maximize your vacation time Cut out the middlemen and minimize costs Plan with professionals having a traveler focussed mindset Be informed with up-to-date advice and honest opinions Enjoy 24&amp;frasl;7 local travel assistance in any destination  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 15:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://satosouthamerica.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>For more information on any of our packages or to get a personalized quote based on your preferences, please get in touch.
Call us toll free on; 1-800-982-0561
Or fill out our contact form and our travel consultants will get in touch;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 15:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://satosouthamerica.com/search/</guid>
      <description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml ` [outputs] home = [&amp;quot;HTML&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;JSON&amp;quot;] \`</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You</title>
      <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 15:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://satosouthamerica.com/thank-you/</guid>
      <description>Thank you, we will be contact soon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Day Argentina Experience</title>
      <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/10-day-argentina-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/10-day-argentina-experience/</guid>
      <description>This trip will allow you to grasp the soul of the massive country and its proud culture. We will start our 10 day Argentina vacation package in the city of Buenos Aires with the Iguazu Falls as your next stop before heading to the far south to explore the beauty of Patagonia, its lakes and glaciers in El Calafate and Ushuaia.
Highlights  Stroll through Recoleta and enjoy Buenos Aires Porteño style; Tango, wine and beef.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Day Bolivia Experience</title>
      <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/10-day-bolivia-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/10-day-bolivia-experience/</guid>
      <description>This week and half will allow you to explore one of South America&amp;rsquo;s best kept secrets; Bolivia. The 10 day Bolivia vacation package starts in breathtaking La Paz will be the starting point of this adventure, exploring the blue waters of lake Titicaca, the beautiful city of Sucre and the unique Uyuni Salt Flats and Siloli Desert.
Highlights  Have your breath taken away by the views of La Paz from a cable car Sail the azure deep blue waters of Lake Titicaca to the Isla del Sol (Sun Island) Walk through the colonial center of Sucre, Bolivia’s second capital Be breath taken by the altitude and the history of Potosi and its (in)famous silver mine Stargaze at the stars reflecting on the shallow waters of the Uyuni Salt Flat at night</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Day Brazil Experience</title>
      <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/10-day-brazil-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/10-day-brazil-experience/</guid>
      <description>This 10 day Brazil vacation package will allow you to get the basics of this South American giant. Everything about Brazil is large; the country, the cities, the carnival,the beaches and jungle&amp;hellip;but mostly the outgoing spirit of its people. Enjoy a little bit of everything that Brazil has to offer.
Highlights  Rio de Janeiro; home to carnival, amazing beaches and 20 million smiles Pics at the foot of the famous Christ statue or on top of the Sugar Loaf Mountain The deafening thunder of the Iguazu Falls when passing underneath in boat Visit some of the countries finest museums in the largest of all cities; São Paulo Discover the depths of the Brazilian Amazon Forest and its massive river  Day by Day Day 1; Welcome enigmatic Rio de Janeiro!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Day Chile Experience</title>
      <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/10-day-chile-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/10-day-chile-experience/</guid>
      <description>During this 10 day Chile vacation package you will have the chance to get to know some of Chile’s most enigmatic destinations and attractions. From the metropolitan capital Santiago we will head north to the Atacama Desert for amazing days and spectacular nights. From here we will head to the far south to explore the granite mountain peaks of the famous Torres del Paine Park in Patagonia
Highlights  Enjoy cultural Santiago perched between the Pacific and the Andes Taste some of Chile’s finest reds and whites at one of the famous Wine Valleys</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Day Chile Wine Experience</title>
      <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/10-day-chile-wine-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/10-day-chile-wine-experience/</guid>
      <description>These 10 days will not only allow to see some of Chile’s most famous sights but also get in depth with one of Chile’s most famous ambassadors; its impressive collection of homegrown wines. From the culinary delights of Santiago we will take you to some of the best wine valleys such as Casablanca, Maipo and Colchagua Valley. You will also get the chance to get to know the coastal cities of Valparaiso and Viña del Mar as well as the Chilean Lake Region around Puerto Varas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Day Ecuador &amp; Galapagos Islands Experience</title>
      <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/10-day-ecuador-galapagos-islands-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/10-day-ecuador-galapagos-islands-experience/</guid>
      <description>This 10 day Ecuador and Galapagos vacation package will allow you to get a great picture of South America’s smallest nation; Ecuador. Incredibly diverse for its size as Darwin himself already noted; Pacific Ocean beaches, skyscraping volcanoes, Colonial cities and the Galapagos Islands with some of the most unique fauna and flora on the planet - Ecuador has it all.
Highlights  Visit the colonial center of Quito, one of the oldest in South America Have one foot in the Southern and one in the Northern Hemisphere at the Equator Enjoy the indiginous market of Otavalo for some serious souvenir shopping Travel over the Vulcano Avenue and through the Waterfall Canyon at Baños Get up close with Giant Turtles and Sea Lions on the Galapagos  Day by Day Day 1; On arrival to Quito we will welcome you and you can relax the rest of the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Day Peru Experience</title>
      <link>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/10-day-peru-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://satosouthamerica.com/package/10-day-peru-experience/</guid>
      <description>These 10 days will allow you to discover the essence of Peru, its archeology and landscapes. Taste the culinary delights of Lima, wander through the cobblestoned streets of Cusco, awe at the beauty of Machu Picchu and spot wildlife in the depths of the Amazon Rainforest.
Highlights  Explore Cosmopolitan Lima Visit colonial Cusco Shop for local textiles on the Pisac market Hike Huayna Picchu for the best views of Machu Picchu below Enjoy the sound, color and smell of the Amazon Rainforest  Day by Day Day 1; On arrival to Lima we will welcome you and take you to your hotel to unwind.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
